mindlabpro.com 2019-02-03

# Privacy Policy | Mind Lab Pro®

This privacy policy sets out how Opti-Nutra LTD uses and protects any information that you give Opti-Nutra LTD when you use this website. This policy only applies to information collected by MindLabPro.com.

This policy discusses:

  * What information is collected from you on this website, and how that information is used.
  * How you can control what data is collected from you by this website
  * Security measures we take to protect your information
  * How you can correct data that may be inaccurate

Opti-Nutra LTD is the sole owner of any information that is collected on MindLabPro.com. We do not sell or rent this information with any party. Information that you share with us is only used to respond to you and your questions, for example, placing an order, inquiring about shipping or asking a question about Mind Lab Pro®.

If you share contact information with us, we may email you in the future with special offers related to Mind Lab Pro®. You can opt out of emails like these at any time.

Opti-Nutra LTD is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Your information

We only collect the basic details required to process your order.

What we do with the information we gather

We will not give your name, address, phone number, email address or any other customer information out to any third party companies, organizations or individuals.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties.

We require your information to process your order and in case there are any problems in the future.

Internal record keeping.

We may use the information to improve our products and services.

We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

Your Ability to Control Your Information

At any point, you may opt out of any contact from this website.

You can also take any of these actions related to your information at any time by [contacting us](https://www.mindlabpro.com/contacts/):

  * See what data has been collected from you, if any
  * Correct or change any data we may have collected about you
  * Direct us to delete any information we may have collected about you
  * Communicate any other concerns you may have about your data

Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties.

How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

We also use Google remarketing cookies to better reach and target our audience. Google remarketing cookies help create an anonymous list of our website's visitors which we can use to market our products and services.

For more information about Google remarketing cookies and how to opt-out, please visit: <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/>

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

Updates

This Privacy Policy may change in the future. All updates will be reflected on this page.

If for any reason you feel Opti-Nutra LTD is not adhering to this Privacy Policy, please [let us know](https://www.mindlabpro.com/contacts/) right away.
